{
  "type": "quiz",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "あか",
      "answer": "red"
    },
    {
      "question": "きいろ",
      "answer": "yellow"
    },
    {
      "question": "しろ",
      "answer": "white"
    },
    {
      "question": "くろ",
      "answer": "black"
    },
    {
      "question": "むらさき",
      "answer": "purple"
    },
    {
      "question": "あお",
      "answer": "blue"
    },
    {
      "question": "みどり",
      "answer": "green"
    },
    {
      "question": "はいいろ",
      "answer": "grey"
    },
    {
      "question": "ちゃいろ",
      "answer": "brown"
    },
    {
      "question": "おれんじ",
      "answer": "orange"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぴんく",
      "answer": "pink"
    }
  ]
}
